Guide to the Stephen M. Cabrinety Collection in the History of Microcomputing, ca. 1975-1995
Department of Special Collections
- Software, Series 1
  - Games, Subseries 1.4
    - Activision, Inc. Human-Like Beings Actually Found Living Inside Computers, 1985, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 111)
    - Activision, Inc. Ice Hockey, n.d., 1 computer cartridgeAtari (Box 152)
    - Activision, Inc. Kaboom!, 1981, 1 computer cartridgeAtari (Box 24)
    - Activision, Inc. Kaboom!, 1982, 1 computer cartridgeAtari (Box 137)
    - Activision, Inc. Keystone Kapers, 1984, 1 computer cartridgeAtari (Box 137)
    - Activision, Inc. Laser Blast, 1981, 1 computer cartridgeAtari (Box 24)
    - Activision, Inc. Little Computer People Discovery Kit, 1986, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 133)
    - Activision, Inc. Malibu Beach Volleyball, 1990, 1 computer cartridgeGame Boy (Nintendo) (Box 204)
    - Activision, Inc. Master of the Lambs, 1985, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 111)
    - Activision, Inc. Master of the Lamps, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 140)
    - Activision, Inc. Master of the Lamps, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 154)
    - Activision, Inc. MegaMania, 1983, 1 computer cartridgeAtari (Box 127)
    - Activision, Inc. Megamania, 1983, 1 computer cartridgeAtari (Box 150)
    - Activision, Inc. Mindshadow, 1985, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 42)
    - Activision, Inc. Mindshadow, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 148)
    - Activision, Inc. Mindshadow, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 177)
    - Activision, Inc. Mindshadow: a text adventure, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 48)
    - Activision, Inc. Mondu's Fight Palace, 1989, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 180)
    - Activision, Inc. Ocean Ranger, 1988, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 195)
    - Activision, Inc. Pastfinder, 1984, 1 computer cartridgeAtari (Box 129)
    - Activision, Inc. Pitfall!, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 136)
    - Activision, Inc. Pitfall!/ Demon Attack, 1982, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 33)
    - Activision, Inc. Pitfall! (Pitfall Harry's Jungle Adventure), 1982, 1 computer cartridgeAtari (Box 24)
    - Activision, Inc. Power Drift, 1990, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 33)
    - Activision, Inc. Power Drift, 1990, 2 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 98)
    - Activision, Inc. Powerhits Battletech, 1992, computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.DOS (Box 164)
    - Activision, Inc. Powerhits Scifi, 1992, computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.DOS (Box 164)
    - Activision, Inc. Pressure Cooker, 1983, 1 computer cartridgeAtari (Box 152)
    - Activision, Inc. Pressure Cooker, 1983, 1 computer cartridgeAtari (Box 218)
    - Activision, Inc. Pro Golf by Tom Weiskopf, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 156)
    - Activision, Inc. Rampage, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 68)
    - Activision, Inc. Rampage, n.d., computer disk; 5 ¼ in.; 3 ½ in.Apple (Box 107)
    - Activision, Inc. River Raid, 1982, computer cartridgeAtari (Box 145)
    - Activision, Inc. Road Race, n.d., 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 129)
    - Activision, Inc. Rock n' Bolt, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 34)
    - Activision, Inc. Shanghai, 1986, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. DOS (Box 68)
    - Activision, Inc. Shanghai, 1986, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 97)
    - Activision, Inc. Shanghai, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 116)
    - Activision, Inc. Shanghai, 1988, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 195)
    - Activision, Inc. Shanghai Demo Version, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Activision, Inc. Shanghai II: Dragon's Eye, 1994, 1 computer cartridgeSega Genesis (Box 207)
    - Activision, Inc. Shark! Shark!, 1982, 1 computer cartridgeAtari (Box 218)
    - Activision, Inc. Space Shuttle: A Journey into Space, 1983, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 105)
    - Activision, Inc. Space Shuttle: A Journey into Space, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 135)
    - Activision, Inc. Space Shuttle: A Journey into Space, 1983, computer cartridgeAtari (Box 145)
    - Activision, Inc. Space Shuttle: A Journey into Space, 1983, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 199)
    - Activision, Inc. Spindizzy, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 200)
    - Activision, Inc. Stampede, 1982, 1 computer cartridgeIntellivision (Box 126)
    - Activision, Inc. Stampede, 1982, 1 computer cartridgeAtari (Box 218)
    - Activision, Inc. Star Rank Boxing, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 195)
    - Activision, Inc. Star Rank Boxing II, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 116)
    - Activision, Inc. Star Rank Boxing II, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 195)
    - Activision, Inc. Starmaster, 1982, 1 computer cartridgeAtari (Box 24)
    - Activision, Inc. The Activision Decathalon, n.d., computer cartridgeAtari (Box 145)
    - Activision, Inc. The Designer's Pencil, 1984, Apple (Box 106)
    - Activision, Inc. The Designer's Pencil, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 187)
    - Activision, Inc. The Dreadnaught Factor by Tom Loughry, n.d., computer cartridgeAtari (Box 145)
    - Activision, Inc. The Kristal, 1989, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 136)
    - Activision, Inc. The Last Ninja, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 196)
    - Activision, Inc. The Music Studio, 1986, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 99)
    - Activision, Inc. The Rocky Horror Show, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 200)
    - Activision, Inc. The Tracer Sanction: an illustrated text adventure, 1984, Apple (Box 106)
    - Activision, Inc. The Transformers: More than meets the eye!, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 194)
    - Activision, Inc. Tongue of the Fatman, 1989, 2 computer disk; 5 ¼ in.; 3 ½ in.DOS (Box 166)
    - Activision, Inc. Toy Bizarre, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 182)
    - Activision, Inc. Tracer Sanction: an illustrated text adventure, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 18)
    - Activision, Inc. Tracer Sanction: an illustrated text adventure, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 37)
    - Activision, Inc. Tracer Sanction: an illustrated text adventure, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 177)
    - Activision, Inc. Web Dimension, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 187)
    - Activision, Inc. Zak McKracken and the Alien Mindbenders, 1989, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 151)
    - Activision, Inc. Zenji, 1984, 1 computer cartridgeAtari (Box 147)
    - Activision, Inc. Zenjin, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 193)
    - Activision, Inc. Zoids, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 200)
    - Addictive Games Aquanaut, 1989, computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 103)
    - Addison -Wesley Publishing Company, Inc. The Fellowship of the Ring, n.d., 2 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 196)
    - Adventure International #10 Adventure by Scott Adams: Savage Island [3 copies], n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 118)
    - Adventure International 3-D Tic-Tac-Toe, 1981, 1 computer cassetteAtari (Box 80)
    - Adventure International Adventure Special Sampler, 1980, 1 computer cartridgeAtari (Box 131)
    - Adventure International Adventureland Special Sampler (2 copies), 1980, 1 computer cassetteAtari (Box 134)
    - Adventure International Adventures of Buckaroo Banzai across the 8th dimension!, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 134)
    - Adventure International Apple Spice [2 copies], 1981, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 124)
    - Adventure International Arex, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 193)
    - Adventure International Bug Off!, 1982, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 124)
    - Adventure International C'est la Vie, 1983, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 110)
    - Adventure International C'est la Vie, 1983, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 126)
    - Adventure International C'est la Vie [2 copies], 1983, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 156)
    - Adventure International Commbat [sic], 1982, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 120)
    - Adventure International Commbat [sic], 1982, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 124)
    - Adventure International Commbat [sic], 1982, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 124)
    - Adventure International Commbat [sic], 1981, 1 computer cassetteAtari (Box 131)
    - Adventure International Deflection and Simon Says, 1980, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 129)
    - Adventure International Earthquake San Francisco 1906, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 107)
    - Adventure International Earthquake San Francisco 1906, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 123)
    - Adventure International Eliminator, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 111)
    - Adventure International Eliminator, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 115)
    - Adventure International Eliminator, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 126)
    - Adventure International Eliminator, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 203)
    - Adventure International Escape from TRAAM!, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 46)
    - Adventure International Escape from TRAAM!, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 124)
    - Adventure International Fire Copter, 1982, 1 computer cassetteTRS-80 (Box 214)
    - Adventure International Galactic Trader, 1981, 1 computer cassetteAtari (Box 134)
    - Adventure International Ghost Town, 1979, 1 computer cassetteAtari (Box 134)
    - Adventure International Kid Venture #1: Little Red Riding Hood, 1980, 1 computer cassetteTRS-80 (Box 215)
    - Adventure International Kingdom of Myrrh: Kingdom of Facts, 1984, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 126)
    - Adventure International Kingdom of Myrrh: Kingdom of Facts [2 copies], 1984, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 110)
    - Adventure International Labyrinth of Crete by Cliff Johnson and Allen Pinero, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 120)
    - Adventure International Labyrinth of Crete by Cliff Johnson and Allen Pinero [2 copies], n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 124)
    - Adventure International Lunar, 1981, 1 computer cassetteTRS-80 (Box 215)
    - Adventure International Maxi Golf, 1984, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 110)
    - Adventure International Maxi Golf, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 193)
    - Adventure International Maxi Golf, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 203)
    - Adventure International Mountain Shoot, n.d., 1 computer cassetteAtari (Box 127)
    - Adventure International Mystery Fun House, 1981, 1 computer cassetteAtari (Box 134)
    - Adventure International Olin in Emerald: Kingdom of Myrrh, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 106)
    - Adventure International Olin in Emerald: Kingdom of Myrrh, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 156)
    - Adventure International Preppie!, 1982, 1 computer cassetteAtari (Box 152)
    - Adventure International Questprobe featuring Human Torch and the Thing, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 134)
    - Adventure International Rear Guard, 1982, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 108)
    - Adventure International Rear Guard, 1982, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 120)
    - Adventure International Rear Guard, 1982, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 124)
    - Adventure International Rear Guard, 1982, computer cassetteAtari (Box 152)
    - Adventure International S.A.G.A. #1: Adventureland, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 55)
    - Adventure International S.A.G.A. #1: Adventureland, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 123)
    - Adventure International S.A.G.A. #2: Pirate Adventure, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 55)
    - Adventure International S.A.G.A. #2: Pirate Adventure, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 123)
    - Adventure International S.A.G.A. #2: Pirate Adventure, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 124)
    - Adventure International S.A.G.A. #2: Pirate Adventure, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 126)
    - Adventure International S.A.G.A. #3: Mission Impossible, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 34)
    - Adventure International S.A.G.A. #3: Mission Impossible, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 120)
    - Adventure International S.A.G.A. #3: Mission Impossible [2 copies], n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 123)
    - Adventure International S.A.G.A. #4: Voodoo Castle, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 34)
    - Adventure International S.A.G.A. #5 Adventure by Scott Adams: The Count, 1979, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 116)
    - Adventure International S.A.G.A. #5 Adventure by Scott Adams: The Count, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 127)
    - Adventure International Savage Island Part One, 1981, 1 computer cassetteAtari (Box 131)
    - Adventure International Savage Island Part Two (2 copies), 1981, 1 computer cassetteAtari (Box 134)
    - Adventure International Scott Adams' Adventure Series: Adventures # 1 - 12 (2 copies), 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 187)
    - Adventure International Scott Adams' Adventure Series Limited Gold Edition Atari 32K Disk, autographed and individually numbered, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 139)
    - Adventure International Scott Adams presents a Marvel Adventure: Questprobe featuring the Hulk, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 106)
    - Adventure International Scott Adams presents a Marvel Adventure: Questprobe, featuring the Human Torch and the Thing, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 121)
    - Adventure International Scott Adams presents a Marvel Adventure: Questprobe featuring Spider-Man, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 126)
    - Adventure International Scott Adams presents a Marvel Adventure: Questprobe featuring the Hulk, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 126)
    - Adventure International Scott Adams presents a Marvel Adventure: Questprobe featuring Spider-Man, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 135)
    - Adventure International Scott Adams presents a Marvel Adventure: Questprobe, featuring the Human Torch and the Thing [2 copies], 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 145)
    - Adventure International Scott Adams presents a Marvel Adventure: Questprobe featuring the Hulk, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 156)
    - Adventure International Scott Adams presents a Marvel Adventure: Questprobe featuring Spider-Man, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 156)
    - Adventure International Scott Adams presents The Sorcrerer of Claymorgue Castle, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 126)
    - Adventure International Scott Adams presents The Sorcrerer of Claymorgue Castle [2 copies], n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 106)
    - Adventure International Scott Adams presents The Sorcrerer of Claymorgue Castle [2 copies], n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 203)
    - Adventure International Scott Adams presents The Sorcrerer of Claymorgue Castle [3 copies], n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 156)
    - Adventure International Sea Dragon, 1981, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 35)
    - Adventure International Sea Dragon, 1982, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 123)
    - Adventure International Sea Dragon, 1982, 1 computer cassetteAtari (Box 129)
    - Adventure International Sea Dragon, 1983, 1 computer cassetteCommodore (Box 199)
    - Adventure International Sea Dragon (2 copies), 1982, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 55)
    - Adventure International Secret Mission S.A.G.A. [Scott Adams Graphic Adventure] #3, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 107)
    - Adventure International Stone of Sisyphus, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 57)
    - Adventure International Stone of Sisyphus, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 107)
    - Adventure International Stone of Sisyphus, 1981, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 149)
    - Adventure International Stone of Sisyphus, 1981, 1 computer cassetteAtari (Box 149)
    - Adventure International Straetos, 1982, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 140)
    - Adventure International Straetos, 1982, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. TRS-80 (Box 214)
    - Adventure International Strange Odyssey S.A.G.A. [Scott Adams Graphic Adventure] #6, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 107)
    - Adventure International Strange Odyssey S.A.G.A. [Scott Adams Graphic Adventure] #6, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 126)
    - Adventure International Strange Odyssey S.A.G.A. [Scott Adams Graphic Adventure] #6, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 139)
    - Adventure International The Adventures of Buckaroo Banzai Across the 8th Dimension!, 1984, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 168)
    - Adventure International The Count S.A.G.A. [Scott Adams Graphic Adventure] #5, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 107)
    - Adventure International The Count S.A.G.A. [Scott Adams Graphic Adventure] #5, 1982, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 120)
    - Adventure International The Curse of Crowley Manor, 1983, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 126)
    - Adventure International The Curse of Crowley Manor [2 copies], 1983, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 110)
    - Adventure International The Eliminator, 1981, 1 computer cassetteTRS-80 (Box 215)
    - Adventure International The Sorcerer of Claymorgue Castle, 1986, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 168)
    - Adventure International Treasure Quest, 1981, 1 computer cassetteAtari (Box 149)
    - Adventure International Triad, 1983, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple; Atari (Box 110)
    - Adventure International Triad, 1983, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple; Atari (Box 123)
    - Adventure International Tunnel Terror, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 124)
    - Adventure International Voodoo Castle S.A.G.A. [Scott Adams Graphic Adventure] #4, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 107)
    - Adventure International Voodoo Castle S.A.G.A. [Scott Adams Graphic Adventure] #4, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 126)
    - Adventure International Voodoo Castle S.A.G.A. [Scott Adams Graphic Adventure] #4, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 152)
    - Adventure International War, 1982, 1 computer cassetteAtari (Box 134)
    - Adventure International Whomper Stomper, 1984, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 126)
    - Adventure International Whomper Stomper, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 134)
    - Adventure International Whomper Stomper [2 copies], 1984, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 110)
    - Adventure International Whomper Stomper [2 copies], 1984, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 156)
    - Aegis Development, Inc. Mac Challenger Space Shuttle Flight Simulation for the Macintosh, 1985, computer disk; 3 ½ in. Macintosh (Box 116)
    - Aegis Development, Inc. Pyramid of Peril, 1985, 2 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Macintosh (Box 121)
    - Aim Software Distribution, Inc. Mars Marauders, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. TRS-80 (Box 25)
    - Aloha Fonts Uncle D's Con Sound Tration, 1987, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 101)
    - Aloha Fonts Uncle D's Con Sound Tration, 1987, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 102)
    - Alpha Software Corporation Alpha Four Demo Disk, 1990, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 161)
    - Alternative Reality Software The I Ching: The Ancient Chinese Book of Divination, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 152)
    - Amazing Software Dan Dare: Pilot of the Future, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 192)
    - American Educational Computer, Inc. Dragon Strike: A Dragonlance action game (Official Advanced Dungeons & Dragons video game) Version, 1992, computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 10)
    - American Educational Computer, Inc. Elementary Science Facts, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 193)
    - American Educational Computer, Inc. Vocabulary Builder, 1988, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 58)
    - American Laser Games Who Shot Johnny Rock?, 1993, 1 computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.Sega (Box 207)
    - American Peripherals Diagram- Sent, 1981, 1 computer cassetteCommodore VIC-20 (Box 211)
    - American Peripherals My Body, 1981, 1 computer cassetteCommodore VIC-20 (Box 212)
    - American Peripherals V56 Tachistoscope, 1981, 1 computer cassetteCommodore VIC-20 (Box 211)
    - American Sammy Corporation Michael Andretti's World GP, 1989, 1 computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 205)
    - American Sammy Corporation Ninja Crusaders, 1990, 1 computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 202)
    - American Sammy Corporation Rolan's Curse, 1990, computer cartridgeGame Boy (Nintendo) (Box 8)
    - American Sammy Corporation Thundercade, 1989, 1 computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 205)
    - American Software Design & Distribution Barnyard Fun, 1981, 1 computer cassetteTexas Instruments 99/4(A) (Box 77)
    - American Software Design Distribution Wizard's Dominion, 1982, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Texas Instruments 99/4(A) (Box 78)
    - American Software Design Distribution Wizard's Dominion, 1982, 1 computer cassetteTexas Instruments 99/4(A) (Box 78)
    - American Softworks Corp. Treasure Master: the ultimate competition for fantasy prizes (notice the "typical american" boy on the cover...), 1991, computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 11)
    - American Video Entertainment, Inc. Deathbots, 1991, 1 computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 202)
    - American Video Entertainment, Inc. Double Strike, 1990, 1 computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 202)
    - American Video Entertainment, Inc. Dudes With Attitude, n.d., 1 computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 202)
    - American Video Entertainment, Inc. F-15 City War, 1990, 1 computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 202)
    - American Video Entertainment, Inc. Impossible Mission II, 1989, 1 computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 202)
    - American Video Entertainment, Inc. Krazy Kreatures, 1990, 1 computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 202)
    - American Video Entertainment, Inc. Puzzle, 1990, 1 computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 202)
    - American Video Entertainment, Inc. Pyramid, 1990, 1 computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 202)
    - American Video Entertainment, Inc. Ultima Exodus, 1988, 1 computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 202)
    - American Video Entertainment, Inc. Ultimate League Soccer, 1990, 1 computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 202)
    - American Video Entertainment, Inc. Venice Beach Volleyball, 1991, 1 computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 202)
    - Amulet Enterprises Galaxy Defender/ Nuke Sub, 1981, 1 computer cassetteAtari (Box 79)
    - Amulet Enterprises Galaxy Defender/ Nuke Sub, 1981, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 85)
    - Analog Software Buried Bucks, 1982, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Analog Software Star Sentry, 1982, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 152)
    - Analog Software Star Sentry, 1982, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 156)
    - Angelsoft, Inc. Goldfinger: James Bond 007, 1986, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 123)
    - Angelsoft, Inc. Goldfinger: James Bond 007, 1986, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 166)
    - Angelsoft, Inc. James Bond 007: A View to Kill, 1985, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Macintosh (Box 6)
    - Angelsoft, Inc. James Bond 007: A View to Kill, 1985, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Macintosh (Box 50)
    - Angelsoft, Inc. James Bond 007: A View to Kill, 1985, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Macintosh (Box 120)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. ADVSYS The Adventure system, 1985, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 93)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. ANTIC Public Domain: ST doodle plus source, n.d., 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 93)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. ANTIC Public Domain: STerminal plus source, n.d., 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 93)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Antic ST Section Compendium 4, 1985, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 93)